Guide to the Andrew F. Smith Collection of Cookery Ephemera MSS.295
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Cookery Ephemera, 1798-2009
  - Longmans, Green & Company, 1935 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    Gas Company. Be an Artist at the Gas Range by "The Mystery Chef" A Complete Cookbook of Successful Recipes. Place of publication unknown: Longmans, Green & Co., 1935.
    Gas Company. Be an Artist at the Successful Recipes by the Mystery Chef. Place of publication unknown: Longman, Green & Co., 1936.
  - Lovelace, Charles D., circa 1930 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Lust, Louise, 1907 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Lydia E. Pinkham Medicine Company, 1927-circa 1930s (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
    Pinkham. Hints for Food and Health. Lynn, MA: Lydia E. Pinkham Medicine Co., undated.
    Pinkham. Come into the Kitchen. Lynn, MA: Lydia E. Pinkham Medicine Co., undated.
    Pinkham. Food and Health. Lynn, MA: Lydia E. Pinkham Medicine Co., undated.
  - Mackintosh & Company, 1888 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Madam Brand Crab Company, circa 1900 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    Madam Brand Crab. Recipes Madam Brand Crab "The Queen of Sea Foods." Japan: Madam Brand Crab, undated.
  - Maine Department of Agriculture, circa 1940s (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Maine Development Commission. Delicious Maine Foods Prepared the Maine Way. Augusta, ME: Maine Development Commission, State Department of Agriculture, undated.
    Maine Department of Agriculture. Potatoes: Facts and Flavor. Fifth Edition. Augusta, ME: Maine Department of Agriculture, undated.
    Maine Dept. of Sea and Shore Fisheries. How to Prepare Maine Lobster. Augusta, ME: Maine Dept. of Sea and Shore Fisheries, undated.
    Maine Dept. of Sea and Shore Fisheries. How to Eat Maine Lobster. Augusta, ME: Maine Dept. of Sea and Shore Fisheries, undated.
  - Majestic Manufacturing Company, circa 1890 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Majestic Manufacturing Co. Majestic Cook Book. St. Louis, MO: Majestic Manufacturing Co., circa 1890.
  - The Malleable Steel Range Manufacturing Company, circa 1900 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Malleable Steel Range Manufacturing. Co. Hiller, A. The Malleable Cook Book. South Bend, IN: The Malleable Steel Range Manufacturing Co., undated.
    Malleable Steel Range Manufacturing Co. Hillier, Ida A., comp. The All-Ways Preferable Cook Book Select Cooking Recipes. South Bend, IN: Malleable Steel Range Manufacturing Co., undated.
  - Marden & Rowell, 1875 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Marion-Kay Company, Inc., 1972 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    Marion-Kay Flavors and Spices. The Star Spangled Season. A Women's Department Program at the 1972 Indiana State Fair. Brownstown, IN: Marion-Kay Flavors and Spices, 1972.
  - Marshall's Saratoga Potato Chips; Martin & Clough, 1858, circa 1890s (Box 24, Folder 9)
    Marshall's Saratoga Potato Chips. Best Potato Chips in the Market. Place of publication unknown: Marshall's Saratoga Potato Chips, undated.
  - The Marvelli Company; Mary Elizabeth Candy Kitchen, 1900, 1907 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    Marvelli Co. Rorer, Sarah Tyson, ed. More than Sixty Ways to Cook Marvelli & Macaroni. Detroit, MI: The Marvelli Co., 1900.
  - Massachusetts Board of Food Administration, 1918, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    Massachusetts Fisheries Association. Choice Recipes of Fish and Sea Foods. Boston, MA: Massachusetts Fisheries Association, 1942.
  - Matthews-Northrup Company; William Wilkins, Jr.-- H-O, circa 1900 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Mawer-Gulden-Annis, Inc.--Grandee Olive Butter, circa 1920s (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Mayor Mitchel's Food Supply Committee, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - McBirney, Mrs. Samuel Pendleton, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    The Chicadees. Nettie McBirney (mrs. Samuel Pendleton McBirney). Aunt Chick's Pies. Tulsa, OK: Chicadees, 1941.
  - McCormick & Company; McCray, Doris-- Helps for Exhibitions at Country Fairs, 1919, circa 1929 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    McCormick & Co. Story of Extracts. Baltimore, MD: McCormick & Co., 1919.
  - McDonald Drug Company, 1890 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    McDonald Drug Co. Our Ladies Book. New York, NY: McDonald Drug Co., 1890.
  - McDowell, Mrs. M. H., circa 1900 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - The McIlhenny Company, circa 1950s-1971 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    McIlhenny Co. Now You're Cooking! See What a Delicious Difference Tabasco Makes in Food!. Place of publication unknown: McIlhenny Co, undated.
    McIlhenny Co. Serve Food with a Flair. Place of publication unknown: McIlhenny Co, undated.
  - McMonagle & Rogers, circa 1888 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    McMonagle & Rogers. Cooking Recipes. Middletown, NY: McMonagle & Rogers, after 1888.
  - M. C. Morgan--Morgan & Winslow, 1828 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Mead Johnson & Company--Sustacal, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Meadow Grove Brand Full Cream Cheese, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    Meadow Grove Brand Full Cream Cheese. Recipes. Meadow Grove, WI: Meadow Grove Brand Full Cream Cheese, undated.
  - Meloripe Fruit Company, 1938-circa 1940s (Box 24, Folder 23)
    Meloripe. Banana Salad Bazaar. Boston, MA: Meloripe Company, undated.
  - Melrose Free Press, Inc.-- The Candy Treat: Sweets to the Sweet, circa 1850s (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Memorial Presbyterian Church, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Mercury Publishing Company, 1876 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Meredith Corporation-- Better Homes & Gardens, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Merrell-Soule Company, 1898 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Merrell-Soule Co. None Such Mindreader. Syracuse, NY: The Merrell-Soule Co., Inc., 1898.
    Merrell-Soule Co. None Such Recipes. New York, NY: The Merrell Soule Co., Inc., undated.
    Merrell-Soule Company. Good Pies Easy to Make. Second Edition. Syracuse, NY: Merrell-Soule Company, undated.
  - Metcalf & Luther's Cook Book, 1883 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, 1911, 1918, 1948-1966 (Box 25, Folder 4-6)
    Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Metropolitan Receipt Book. New York, NY: Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, 1911.
    Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Metropolitan Life Cook Book. New York, NY: Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, 1918.
    Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Metropolitan Life Cook Book. New York, NY: Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, undated.
    Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Metropolitan Cook Book. New York, NY: Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, 1948.
    Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Metropolitan Cook Book. New York, NY: Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, 1953.
    Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Metropolitan Cook Book. New York, NY: Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, 1957.
    Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Metropolitan Cook Book. New York, NY: Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, undated.
  - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - The Methodist Church--West Rindge, NH, 1891 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Michigan Bean Commission, circa 1970s (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Michigan Bean Commission. Beans Grown in Michigan–Enjoyed the World Over. Lansing, MI: Michigan Bean Commission, undated.
  - Michigan Consolidated Gas Company, 1966-1969 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - The Michigan Stove Company, 1905 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Garland Stoves and Ranges. Convenience and Economy are Secured by Using Garland Gas Ranges. Detroit and Chicago: The Michigan Stove Company, 1905.
  - Middleton, Carman & Company, 1887 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Midland Flour Milling Company, circa 1930s (Box 25, Folder 13)
    Midland Flour Milling Co. Town Crier Baking Guide. Kansas City, MO: Midland Flour Milling Co., undated.
  - Miles Laboratories, Inc., circa 1952 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    Miles Laboratories. 20th Anniversary Souvenir One Man's Family Mother Barbour's Favorite Recipes. Elkhart, IN: Miles Laboratories, Inc., circa 1952.
  - Miles Laboratories, Inc., undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
    Modern Household Hints
  - Millswood, G., circa 1830s (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Min Sun Trading Company; The Milnot Company, circa 1933, circa 1960-1970s (Box 25, Folder 16)
    Milnot Co. Prize Winning Recipes. Litchfield, IL: Milnot Co., undated.
    Min Sun Trading Company. "Chinese Maid." Chop Suey, Chow Mein and Egg Foo Yong, etc. Chicago, IL: Min Sun Trading Company, circa 1933.
  - Minute Tapioca Company, 1926-1934 (Box 25, Folder 17-18)
    Minute Tapioca Company. The Story of Tapioca. Orange, MA: Minute Tapioca Company, Inc., undated.
    Minute Tapioca Company. Minute Gelatine Cook Book. Orange, MA: Minute Tapioca Company, 1926.
    Minute Tapioca Co., Inc. Faster Ways to Favorite Dishes with the New Minute Tapioca. Orange, MA: Minute Tapioca Co., Inc., 1934.
    Minute Tapioca Company. Prize Winning Recipes to Vary Your Menus. Orange, MA: Minute Tapioca Company, Inc., 1927.
    Minute Tapioca Company. A Cook's Tour with Minute Tapioca. Orange, MA: Minute Tapioca Company, 1929.
  - Mirro Aluminum Company, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Miss Farmer's School of Cookery, 1907 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - M. J. Ivers & Company, 1882 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Monterey Packing Company; Modern Magazines, circa 1900-1930s (Box 25, Folder 22)
    Modern Magazines. The Modern Hostess Recipe Book; 72 Favorite Dishes of Hollywood. New York, NY: Modern Magazines, undated.
    Monterey Packing Co. Booth's Sardines Crescent Brand. Monterey, CA: Monterey Packing Co., circa 1900.
  - Montgomery, Ward & Company, 1915-1916, circa 1920-1940s (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
    Montgomery, Ward & Co. Groceries November-December 1915. New York, NY: Montgomery, Ward & Co., 1915.
    Montgomery, Ward & Co. Groceries September-October 1916, New York. New York: Montgomery, Ward & Co., 1916.
    Montgomery, Ward & Co. Cold Cooking It's Easy More than 150 Approved Recipes. Place of publication unknown: Montgomery, Ward & Co., Inc., undated.
    Montgomery, Ward & Co. Montgomery Wards Magic Seal Pressure Canner Instruction and Recipes. Recipe Book War Model No. 2. Place of publication unknown: Montgomery, Ward. & Co., undated.
  - Moseley & Stoddard Manufacturing Company, 1881 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Mrs. D. A. Lincoln, 1889 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    White Mountain Freezer. Lincoln, Mary J., ed. Frozen Dainties. Nashua, NH: White Mountain Freezer Co, 1889. Reprint Bedford, Massachusetts: Applewood Books, undated.
    White Mountain Freezer. Lincoln, Mary J., ed. Frozen Dainties. Nashua, NH: White Mountain Freezer Co., 1892.
  - Mrs. Mary J. Lincoln, 1889 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    Mrs. Lincoln's Baking Powder Co. Lincoln, Mary J. Mrs. Lincoln's Baking Powder Company Cook Book. Boston, MA: Mrs. Lincoln's Baking Powder Co., 1899.
    Mrs. Lincoln's Baking Powder Co. Lincoln, Mary J. A Cook Book for a Month at a Time. Boston, MA: Mrs Lincoln's Baking Powder Co, 1899.
  - Mrs. Winslow, 1862-1879, 1885, 1892 (Box 26, Folder 6-10)
  - Mt. Mansfield Maple Merchants, 1929-1930 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    The Sweetest Story Ever Told
  - Muller, J., 1910 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Mueller's Egg Noodles; Mount Vernon Cream Company, circa 1900, circa 1920s (Box 26, Folder 12)
    Mount Vernon Cream Co. Mount Vernon Milk Recipe Book. Seattle, WA: Mount Vernon Cream Co., undated.
    Mueller's Egg Noodles. Mueller's Modern Process Egg Noodles. Place of publication unknown: Mueller's Egg Noodles, undated.
  - Murray, Mary B., 1935 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Food (Appointment Calendar)
  - Nabisco, Inc., 1974 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    Nabisco. 40 Ritzy Recipes with Ritz Crackers. Chicago, IL: Nabisco, 1974.
  - Nash-Kelvinator Corporation, circa 1950s (Box 26, Folder 15)
    Nash-Kelvinator. The Kelvinator Book of Kitchen Tested Recipes. Detroit, MI: Nash-Kelvinator, undated.
    Kelvinator. 23 Delicious Dishes from 4 Frozen "Starters." Place of publication unknown: Kelvinator Institute for Better Living, undated.
  - Nashville-Chattanooga & St. Louis Railway, circa 1918 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    Nashville-Chattanooga & St. Louis Railroad. Peanut and Soya Bean Oil Manufacture. Nashville, TN: Nashville-Chattanooga & St. Louis Railroad, circa 1918.
  - National Biscuit Company, 1921 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    National Biscuit Company. National Bread in One Hundred Dainty Dishes. Place of publication unknown: National Biscuit Company, 1921.
  - National Cherry Festival, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    National Cherry Festival. The 44th National Cherry Festival 1969 Official Souvenir Program. Traverse City, MI: National Cherry Festival, 1969.
  - National Dairy Council; Miami Valley Co-Operative Milk Producers Association, 1923, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    National Dairy Council. Lunchtime on the Home Front. Chicago, IL: National Dairy Council, 1942.
    Miami Valley Co-Operative Milk Producers Association. Dayton Dairy Made Butter. Dayton, OH: Miami Valley Co-operative Milk Producers Assn., 1923.
  - National Emergency Food Garden Commission, 1917 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - National Live Stock & Meat Board, 1927-1934, circa 1940-1950s (Box 26, Folder 21, Box 27, Folder 1-3)
    National Live Stock and Meat Board. Meat Recipes and Menus 1931. Chicago, IL: National Live Stock and Meat Board, 1930.
    National Live Stock and Meat Board. 101 Meat Recipes Olde and New. Chicago, IL: National Live Stock and Meat Board, 1927.
    National Live Stock and Meat Board. Meat for Health. Chicago, IL: National Live Stock and Meat Board, undated.
    National Live Stock and Meat Board. Mealtime USA. Chicago, IL: National Live Stock and Meat Board, undated.
    National Live Stock and Meat Board. Foods with a Flair Cook Book. Chicago, IL: National Live Stock and Meat Board, undated.
    National Live Stock and Meat Board. Fantasy of Foods Cook Book. Chicago, IL: National Live Stock and Meat Board, undated.
    National Live Stock and Meat Board. Portraits in Food. Chicago, IL: National Live Stock and Meat Board, undated.
    National Live Stock and Meat Board. Spotlight on Food. Chicago, IL: National Live Stock and Meat Board, undated.
    National Live Stock and Meat Board. Meat Recipes to Please. Chicago, IL: National Live Stock and Meat Board, 1954-55.
  - National Onion Salt Company; National Onion Institute, circa 1900, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    National Onion Institute. Know Your Onions 15 Different Recipes. St. Louis, MO: National Onion Institute, 1935.
    National Onion Salt Company. National Onion Salt Company's Cook Book Onion Salt The Universal Food Seasoning. Place of publication unknown: National Onion Salt Company, undated.
  - National Pork Producers Council, undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
    Flavor Fusion
  - National Potato Chip Institute, circa 1930-1940s (Box 27, Folder 5)
    National Potato Chip Institute. "Thank You, Mr. Chips." Cleveland, OH: National Potato Chip Institute, undated.
    National Potato Chip Institute. Potato Chip and Sandwich Tray, Promotional Flyer. Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, undated.
    Potato Chip Institute. Recipes and Party Ideas Starring Potato Chips. Cleveland, OH: Potato Chip Institute, undated.
  - National Pressure Cooker Company, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    National Pressure Cooker Co. National Presto Cooker (Model '60') Recipe Book. Eau Claire, WI: National Pressure Cooker Company, circa 1947.
  - National Presto Industries, Inc., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    National Pressure Cooker Co. Presto Control Master Appliances and Recipe Book. Eau Claire, WI: National Pressure Cooker Company, 1960.
  - National Presto Industries of Canada, Ltd., 1956 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    National Presto Industries. Instructions and Recipes Book Presto Electric Pressure Cooker. Eau Claire, WI: National Presto Industries of Canada Inc., 1956.
  - National Starch Company, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    National Starch Company. Hill, Janet M., and Alice Cary Waterman. Recipes and Cooking Suggestions. New York, NY: National Starch Company, 1907.
  - National Yeast Company, circa 1884-1885 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    National Yeast Co. Cook Book. Seneca Falls, NY: National Yeast Co., circa 1884.
    National Yeast Co. Cook Book. Seneca Falls, NY: National Yeast Co., circa 1885.
  - Natural Food Company, circa 1898-1918 (Box 28, Folder 1-2, Box 27, Folder 11-14)
    Natural Food Company. The Vital Question. Worcester, MA: Cereal Machine Company, circa 1899.
    Natural Food Company. The Vital Question. Niagara, NY: Natural Food Company, circa 1899.
    Natural Food Company. The Vital Question. Niagara, NY: Natural Food Company, circa 1901.
    Natural Food Company. The Vital Question Cook Book. Niagara, NY: Natural Food Company, circa 1902.
    Natural Food Company. The Vital Question. Niagara, NY: Natural Food Company, circa 1904.
    Natural Food Company. The Vital Question Cook-Book. Niagara, NY: Shredded Wheat Company; Niagra, Canada: Canadian Shredded Wheat Company, circa 1909.
    Natural Food Company. Shredded Wheat Dishes; From the Wheat Field to the Table [on the back]: The Vital Question. Niagara Falls, NY: Shredded Wheat Company, 1910.
    Natural Food Company. Getting a Good Start. Niagara Falls, NY: Shredded Wheat Company, 1918.
    Natural Food Co. Triscuit. Niagara Falls, NY: Natural Food Co., circa 1910.
  - Natural Food Company with the Shredded Wheat Company, circa 1910-1920s (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Nebraska Sanatarium Kitchen, undated (Box Shared Fales 002, Folder 10)
  - The N. E. Protective Union; Nestle Food Company, 1857, 1914 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - New England Maple Syrup Company, circa 1900-1920s (Box 28, Folder 4)
    New England Maple Syrup Co. "A Few Good Ways to Use Uncle John's Syrup." Boston, MA: New England Maple Syrup Co., undated.
  - New Family Manual, Or Ladies' Indispensable Assistant, 1851 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - New Federal Canning Company--Barefoot Boy Brand Tomatoes, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - The New York Biscuit Company; New York Art Students League, 1895, circa 1920-1940 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    New York Biscuit Co. Poole, Hester M. Bent & Co.'s Cracker Meal Receipts. Milton, MA: The New York Biscuit Co., 1895.
  - New York Confectioners Guard, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    New York Confectioners Guard. Diamond Jubilee in Commemoration of the Seventy-fifth Anniversary of the New York Confectioners Guard, Hotel Astor, Sunday Evening, December 12, 1937. (Souvenir Program) New York, NY: New York Confectioners Guard, 1937.
  - The New York Cooking School, 1878-1884 (Box 28, Folder 8-9)
  - New York Edison Company, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    New York Edison Company. Electrified Recipes. New York, NY: New York Edison Company, 1923.
  - New York Evening Post, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    New York Evening Post. Morley, Christopher. The Story of Ginger Cubes. New York, NY: New York Evening Post, 1922.
  - New York Produce Exchange Reporter and Price Current, Vol. XII, 1866 (Box Shared Fales 002, Folder 11)
  - New York State Agricultural Society, circa 1926 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - New York World's Fair--Naranjilla Ice Cream, circa 1939 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    Naranjilla. For the First Time in Your Life You are Going to Drink Naranjilla. Hall of Nations, NY World's Fair Printed in Ecuador: publisher unknown, undated.
  - The N. H. Democratic Press Company, 1894 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - The N. K. Fairbank Company, 1903-1907 (Box 43, Folder 7, Box 28, Folder 15)
    N. K. Fairbank Company. Rorer, Sarah Tyson, ed. Home Helps with Illustrations. A Practical & Useful Book of Recipes with Much Valuable Information on Cooking & Serving Breakfasts, Luncheons, Dinners & Teas. Chicago, IL: The N. K. Fairbank Company, 1906
    Fairbank Company. Lincoln, Mary J., ed. Pure Food Cook Book. Chicago, IL: The N. K. Fairbank Company, 1907.
  - Norse Crown Canning Company, Inc.; Nordic Ware, 1924, circa 1950s (Box 28, Folder 16)
    Norse Crown Canning Co. Norse Crown Sea Food Products and Fifty Ways to Serve Them. New York, NY: Norse Crown Canning Co., Inc., 1924.
  - The North American, circa 1900 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    The North American. Thoroughly Tested Cooking Recipes for Cutting Table Expenses One-Half. Philadelphia, PA: The North American, undated.
  - North American Mercantile Company; North American Blueberry Council, circa 1920s, circa 1950-1960s (Box 28, Folder 18)
    North American Blueberry Council. Luscious Great Lakes Blueberries Recipes. Place of publication unknown: North American Blueberry Council, undated.
  - North Brothers Manufacturing Company, circa 1900 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    North Bros. Manufacturing Co. Rorer, S. T. Kitchen Knacks. Philadelphia, PA: North Bros. Manufacturing Co., undated.
  - Northwest Fruit Products Company--Loganberry Juice, circa 1910-1920 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - The Northwestern Consolidated Milling Company, circa 1910-1920 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    Northwestern Consolidated Milling Co. Ceresota Cook Book. Minneapolis, MN: The Northwestern Consolidated Milling Co., undated.
  - Northwestern Steel & Iron Works, circa 1890, circa 1900 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    Northwestern Steel & Iron Works. "National" Steam Pressure Recipes. Eau Claire, WI: Northwestern Steel & Iron Works, undated. circa 1890.
    Northwestern Steel & Iron Works. National Steam Pressure Canning Outfit Catalogue No. 18. Eau Claire, WI: Northwestern Steel & Iron Works, undated. circa 1900.
  - Northwestern Yeast Company, 1921, 1935, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 22, Box 29, Folder 1)
    Northwestern Yeast Company. Magic Yeast Recipes. Chicago, IL: Mcgill Weinstheimer Co., undated.
    Northwestern Yeast Company. Oven Melodies Using Maca Yeast. Chicago, IL: Northwestern Yeast Company, 1939.
    Northwestern Yeast Co. Dry Yeast as an Aid to Health. Chicago, IL: Northwestern Yeast Co., 1921.
    Northwestern Yeast Co. Yeast Foam Recipes. Chicago, IL: Northwestern Yeast Co., undated.
    Northwestern Yeast Co. The Art of Baking Bread. Chicago, IL: Northwestern Yeast Co., 1935.
    Northwestern Yeast Co. The Art of Baking Bread. Chicago, IL: Northwestern Yeast Co., undated.
    Northwestern Yeast Co. The Art of Making Bread at Home. Chicago, IL: Northwestern Yeast Co., 1939.
    Northwestern Yeast Co. The Art of Making Bread. Chicago, IL: Northwestern Yeast Co., undated.
  - Norwegian Canners Association, circa 1950s (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Norwegian Canners Association. Saucier, Ted, comp. Norway Sardine Recipes. New York, NY: Norwegian Canners Association, undated.
  - The Ogilvie Flour Mills Company, Ltd., 1905 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Okra Research, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Old Sturbridge Village, Inc., 1964 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Old Sturbridge Village. "Hot from the Oven.". Meriden, CT: Meriden Gravure Company, 1964.
  - Olivit & Conklin, 1879 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Omron Heathcare, Inc., 2004 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - O. Noble & Company, circa 1850s (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Carter's Compound Extract of Smart Weed. The Housekeeper's Receipt Book. Erie, PA: O. Noble & Co., undated.
  - The Oregon Statesman Free Electric Cooking School, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Oriental Foods, Inc., 1939 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Oriental Tea Company, 1868 (Box Shared Fales 003, Folder 3)
  - Osborn, Grace, 1919 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Oscar & Company Inc., circa 1900 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Otis Sapp & Son, circa 1940-1950s (Box 29, Folder 13)
    Otis Sapp & Son. Non-Fattening, Non-Heating Salads with Supermaise Lobster Salad. Boston, MA & Providence, RI: Otis Sapp & Son, undated.
  - Otto Benz Company, Inc., 1955 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    Otto Benz Co., Inc. Bates, Joseph D., Jr. Outdoor Cooking... Made Easy!. Place of publication unknown: Otto Benz Co., Inc., 1955.
  - Otto Seidner, Inc., 1930, circa 1950 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    Seidner. Seidner's Mayonnaise; A Manual of New Recipes. Westerly, RI: Otto Seidner, Inc., 1930.
    Seidner. Mayonnaise by Seidner. Westerly, RI: Otto Seidner, Inc, circa 1950.
  - Oxo Limited with Lamont Corliss & Company, circa 1910-1920s (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Owen, Mrs. De Witt C., 1898, 1900 (Box 29, Folder 16-17)
  - Ozark Maid Candies, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    Ozark Maid Candies. Ma's Cookin' by "Sis and Jake.". Osage Beach, MO: Ozark Maid Candies, 1966.